<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Soft on ProgramMur - Programmer's Murmur</title><link>https://blog.androchen.tw/en/categories/soft/</link><description>Recent content in Soft on ProgramMur - Programmer's Murmur</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>[CC BY-NC-SA 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/4.0/deed.en)</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 20:54:32 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.androchen.tw/en/categories/soft/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ChatGPT Language Learning: 6 Tips for Utilizing YouTube + Free Plugins to Improve TOEIC Score</title><link>https://blog.androchen.tw/en/chatgpt-learn-language-6-tips-youtube-toeic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 10:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.androchen.tw/en/chatgpt-learn-language-6-tips-youtube-toeic/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="overview">Overview&lt;/h2>
&lt;img style="width:100%;" src="https://github.com/androchentw/blog-hugo/blob/main/content/life/learn-en/2023-05-01-chatgpt-learn-language-6-tips-youtube-toeic-1-overview.en.jpg?raw=true">
&lt;p align="center">&lt;sub>&lt;sup>
 ChatGPT Language Learning
&lt;/sup>&lt;/sub>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I have been actively using ChatGPT to self-study English and Japanese recently.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The main motivation for learning foreign languages is to improve daily conversation and absorb new knowledge from abroad. I also have friends preparing for TOEIC. The primary goal is to &lt;strong>enhance learning efficiency&lt;/strong>, and exploring how to make the best use of new AI technology is fascinating!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Features of the tools introduced today:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>ðŸŒ Free to use online.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>ðŸš€ Generate bilingual subtitles and video summary Mindmap on YouTube with one click and convert them into TOEIC test questions.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>ðŸ“ Combine ChatGPT translation and modification features to create your vocabulary book and essay collection.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>ðŸ¤” Q: How would you use ChatGPT to assist with language learning?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ðŸ’ª A: Choose a YouTube video and generate video summaries and TOEIC learning content in practice.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Today I&amp;rsquo;ll mainly share the English application. Japanese can also be learned similarly, but my approach is slightly different. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested, please let me know by +1 ðŸ˜†&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>3-Minute Infographic - Boost Productivity with ChatGPT + Mermaid</title><link>https://blog.androchen.tw/en/3-minute-infographic-chatgpt-mermaid-productivity/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 10:00:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.androchen.tw/en/3-minute-infographic-chatgpt-mermaid-productivity/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="overview">Overview&lt;/h2>
&lt;img style="width:80%;" src="https://github.com/androchentw/blog-hugo/blob/main/content/soft/productivity/2023-04-20-3-minute-infographic-chatgpt-mermaid-productivity-cover.en.png?raw=true">
&lt;p align="center">&lt;sub>&lt;sup>
 3-Minute Infographic - Boost Productivity with ChatGPT + Mermaid
&lt;/sup>&lt;/sub>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Today I&amp;rsquo;d like to share the diagramming tools I use in practice and how I combine them, hoping to help friends who love using visualization to illustrate their logic.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Actually, diagram-as-code tools have been around for a while; it&amp;rsquo;s just that ChatGPT makes this task even easier.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Features of today&amp;rsquo;s introduced tool:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>ðŸŒ Free to use on a web page.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>ðŸš€ Quickly generate flowcharts, mindmaps, pie charts, Gantt charts, timelines, user journeys, and more.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>ðŸ“ Uses markdown syntax, easy to learn even without an engineering background, convenient for version control.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>ðŸ¤” Q: What kind of charts would you typically use ChatGPT + Mermaid to assist you with in your daily work?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ðŸ’ª A: Choose an example and actually draw a chart using the online editor.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>ProgramMur - Programmer's Murmur Redefine + Newsletter</title><link>https://blog.androchen.tw/en/programmur-redefine-newsletter/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 14:30:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.androchen.tw/en/programmur-redefine-newsletter/</guid><description>&lt;img style="width:60%;" src="https://github.com/androchentw/blog-hugo/blob/main/res/blog-cover-yume.jpg?raw=true">
&lt;p align="center">&lt;sub>&lt;sup>
 Kyoto KÅdai-ji Temple, Hideyoshi Toyotomi, Goshuincho Dream Yume
&lt;/sup>&lt;/sub>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>2023-04-04 A thousand expectations I originally wanted to release on April Fool&amp;rsquo;s Day.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Recently, thanks to ChatGPT, I have made many new friends. I am very grateful for the attention and hope that I can continue to present insightful knowledge points to you. In summary, I will define the positioning of this blog, the content I expect to cover, and try to launch a &lt;a href="https://programmuren.substack.com/">free newsletter&lt;/a>. If you have any feedback or ideas, please feel free to send a private message or email. Let&amp;rsquo;s grow together and explore the journey of technology/life.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ðŸ¤” Q: What knowledge do you want to gain?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>ðŸ’ª A: Subscribe to the &lt;a href="https://programmuren.substack.com/">newsletter&lt;/a>!&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>(2023/04/16) I&amp;rsquo;m an IT engineer from Taiwan ðŸ‡¹ðŸ‡¼. I&amp;rsquo;m using ChatGPT and other software to help translate the original and future valuable articles. If there are any unclear expressions, please feel free to let me know. I&amp;rsquo;m also working hard to learn English and Japanese!&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote></description></item></channel></rss>